#### **Profile**

My name is Sanusi Lamido, I am a 26 year old web developer with a degree in software engineering. I obtained my degree in 2019, and since the I have continuously honed my skills in web development, consistently improving and creating visually appealing, highly functional websites and web applications for clients as a free lancer and for companies as an intern. My experience includes;

## Experience

#### INTERN, NATIONAL CENTER FOR ARTIFICIAL INTELLIGENCE AND ROBOTICS - 2022-PRESENT

- Web development using Wordpress
- Web development using HTML, CSS and JavaScript
- Data Analysis using Pandas

## **WEB DEVELOPER, GET IT SOLUTIONS – 2019-PRESENT**

- Customer relations
- Requirements gathering
- Web Development using CMS
- Web Development using HTML, CSS & JavaScript

# INTERN, (IT UNIT) HIGH COURT OF JUSTICE - 2019-2020

- Web Development using Wordpress
- Website Maintenance
- Cable crimping

#### Education

Baze University, Abuja, Nigeria – B.Sc Software engineering, 2019

National center for Artificial Intelligence and Robotics – Basic Python certificate, 2022

National center for Artificial Intelligence and Robotics – Intermediate Python certificate, 2022

Coursera – IBM Introduction to web development with HTML, CSS & JavaScript Course certificate 2023

## Skills

- HTML
- CSS
- JavaScript
- Wordpress
- Python
- React